Boredom has become trendy.
无聊已经变得时髦起来。
Studies point to how boredom is good for creativity and innovation, as well as mental health.
多项研究指出，无聊有益于创造力和创新，对心理健康也有好处。
It is found that people are more creative following the completion of a tedious task.
研究发现，人们在完成一项乏味的任务之后会更有创造力。
When people are bored, they have an increase in “associative thought”—the process of making new connections between ideas, which is linked to innovative thinking.
人们感到无聊时，“联想思维”会增多——联想思维是在不同想法之间建立新联系的过程，与创新思维有关。
These studies are impressive, but in reality, the benefits of boredom may be related to having time to clear your mind, be quiet, or daydream.
这些研究令人印象深刻，但实际上，无聊的好处可能与有时间放空头脑、安静下来或做白日梦有关。
In our stimulation-rich world, it seems unrealistic that boredom could occur at all.
在我们这个充满刺激的世界里，人居然还会感到无聊，这似乎令人难以置信。
Yet, there are valid reasons boredom may feel so painful.
然而，无聊之所以可能让人感觉如此痛苦，是有其合理原因的。
As it turns out, boredom might signal the fact that you have a need that isn’t being met.
原来，无聊可能表明这样一个事实：你有某种需求没有得到满足。
Our always-on world of social media may result in more connections, but they are superficial and can get in the way of building a real sense of belonging.
我们这个时刻在线的社交媒体世界或许会带来更多的人际联系，但这些联系很肤浅，还可能妨碍我们建立真正的归属感。
Feeling bored may signal the desire for a greater sense of community and the feeling that you fit in with others around you.
感到无聊可能表明，你渴望获得更强的集体感，渴望感到自己能融入身边的人群。
So take the step of joining an organization to build face-to-face relationships.
那就迈出一步，加入一个组织，去建立面对面的人际关系吧。
You’ll find depth that you won’t get from your screen no matter how many likes you get on your post.
你会在这样的关系中体会到一种深度，无论你的帖子收获多少点赞，这都是屏幕给不了你的。
As with the need for belonging, bored people often report that they feel a limited sense of meaning.
和归属需求的情况一样，感到无聊的人常常表示，他们觉得缺少意义感。
It’s a fundamental human need to have a larger purpose and to feel like we’re part of something bigger than ourselves.
拥有更远大的目标，感觉自己是比自身更宏大之物的一部分，这是人类的一种基本需求。
When people are bored, they’re more likely to feel less meaning in their lives.
人们感到无聊时，更有可能觉得自己的生活没那么有意义。
If you want to reduce boredom and increase your sense of meaning, seek work where you can make a unique contribution, or find a cause you can support with your time and talent.
如果你想减少无聊、增强意义感，就去寻找一份能让你做出独特贡献的工作，或者找到一项你可以用自己的时间和才能去支持的事业。
If your definition of boredom is being quiet, mindful, and reflective, keep it up.
如果你对无聊的定义是安静、专注当下、沉思内省，那就继续保持吧。
But if you’re struggling with real boredom and the emptiness it provokes, consider whether you might seek new connections and more significant challenges.
但如果你正苦于真正的无聊以及它引发的空虚感，那就考虑一下，你是否可以去寻求新的人际联系和更有意义的挑战。
These are the things that will genuinely relieve boredom and make you more effective in the process.
正是这些事情会真正缓解无聊，并在此过程中让你做事更有成效。